<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ICCUBEA 2017</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cmt_login">CmtLogin</string>
    <string name="start_title">CmtLogin</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">About</string>
    <string name="title_activity_guidelines">Guidelines</string>
    <string name="title_activity_second">SecondActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_second2">SecondActivity2</string>
    <string name="infoPccoe">Pimpri Chinchwad College of Engineering (PCCoE) is one of the best engineering colleges in India, established in 1999, nurtured and managed by Pimpri Chinchwad Education Trust.\n\nPCCoE is functioning proactively to provide the best professional environment to engineering and Management students in terms of Academics, Industry oriented trainings, Sports, Co-Curricular &amp; Extra Curricular activities, Cultural activities, various competitions, etc to create true aesthetically sensitive, socially committed and technologically competent Engineers and Management professionals.\n\nAcademics at PCCoE is disciplined with results at the par of best colleges in Savitribai Phule Pune University. Students of PCCoE are proving their talents at state and national level competitions for technical and non-technical events. Along with results PCCoE has excellent placement.\n\nThe Output of any Institute is the Input of industry. We sincerely thank our Industrial counterparts who help shaping the industry focused personalities of our students through their direct mentorship and continued interaction.\n\nDr. Ajay M. Fulambarkar, Principal (PCCoE), is a well-known personality of Academic world of Pune and Maharashtra, serving the academy for illustrious more than 33 years. Sir is Executive Member on Board of Student Welfare, SPPU; Executive Council member Quality Circle Forum of India, Pune Chapter; Secretary, Pune Consortium of Principals of Engineering Colleges; and Life Member of ISTE.\n\n<b>Vision</b>\nTo serve the Society, Industry and all stake holders through Value Added Quality Education.\n\n<b>Mission</b>\nTo serve the need of the society at large by establishing state-of-the-art Engineering, Management and Research institute and impart Attitude, Knowledge and Skills with Quality Education to develop individuals and teams with ability to think and analyze right values and self-reliance.\n\n<b>Objective</b>\nTo create aesthetically sensitive, socially committed and technologically competent Engineers and Management professionals.\n\n<b>Quality Policy</b>\nWe at PCCoE are committed to impart Value Added Quality Education to satisfy the needs and expectations of the Students and other Stakeholders. We shall achieve this by establishing and strengthening State-of-the-art Engineering and Management Institute through continual improvement in effective implementation of Quality Management System.\n\n<b>Quality Objectives</b>\nTo enhance students satisfaction.\n\nTo improve satisfaction of faculty and staff through developmental activities.\n\nTo satisfy infra structural requirements.\n\nEffectiveness of interaction with outside world.</string>
    <string name="infoICCUBEA">ICCUBEA is the 3rd International Conference On Computing, Communication, Control And Automation, organized by the Pimpri Chinchwad College Of Engineering. The conference covers areas like High performance Computing, Distributed Systems, Parallel System, Grid and Cloud Computing, Databases, Storage System, Data Mining, Web Mining and Business Intelligence, Soft Computing, Intelligent System, Machine Vision and Artificial Neural Network, Graphics, Image or Video Processing and Human Computer Interface and much more.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_second3">SecondActivity3</string>
    <string name="title_activity_second4">SecondActivity4</string>
    <string name="title_activity_how_too_reach">How To Reach</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_track_your_paper_tabbed">TrackYourPaperTabbed</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>

</resources>
