<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ICCUBEA 2017</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cmt_login">CmtLogin</string>
    <string name="start_title">CmtLogin</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">About</string>
    <string name="title_activity_guidelines">Guidelines</string>
    <string name="title_activity_second">SecondActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_second2">SecondActivity2</string>
    <string name="infoPccoe">Pimpri Chinchwad College of Engineering (PCCoE) is one of the best engineering colleges in India, established in 1999, nurtured and managed by Pimpri Chinchwad Education Trust.\n\nPCCoE is functioning proactively to provide the best professional environment to engineering and Management students in terms of Academics, Industry oriented trainings, Sports, Co-Curricular &amp; Extra Curricular activities, Cultural activities, various competitions, etc to create true aesthetically sensitive, socially committed and technologically competent Engineers and Management professionals.\n\nAcademics at PCCoE is disciplined with results at the par of best colleges in Savitribai Phule Pune University. Students of PCCoE are proving their talents at state and national level competitions for technical and non-technical events. Along with results PCCoE has excellent placement.\n\nThe Output of any Institute is the Input of industry. We sincerely thank our Industrial counterparts who help shaping the industry focused personalities of our students through their direct mentorship and continued interaction.\n\nDr. Ajay M. Fulambarkar, Principal (PCCoE), is a well-known personality of Academic world of Pune and Maharashtra, serving the academy for illustrious more than 33 years. Sir is Executive Member on Board of Student Welfare, SPPU; Executive Council member Quality Circle Forum of India, Pune Chapter; Secretary, Pune Consortium of Principals of Engineering Colleges; and Life Member of ISTE.\n\n<b>Vision</b>\nTo serve the Society, Industry and all stake holders through Value Added Quality Education.\n\n<b>Mission</b>\nTo serve the need of the society at large by establishing state-of-the-art Engineering, Management and Research institute and impart Attitude, Knowledge and Skills with Quality Education to develop individuals and teams with ability to think and analyze right values and self-reliance.\n\n<b>Objective</b>\nTo create aesthetically sensitive, socially committed and technologically competent Engineers and Management professionals.\n\n<b>Quality Policy</b>\nWe at PCCoE are committed to impart Value Added Quality Education to satisfy the needs and expectations of the Students and other Stakeholders. We shall achieve this by establishing and strengthening State-of-the-art Engineering and Management Institute through continual improvement in effective implementation of Quality Management System.\n\n<b>Quality Objectives</b>\nTo enhance students satisfaction.\n\nTo improve satisfaction of faculty and staff through developmental activities.\n\nTo satisfy infra structural requirements.\n\nEffectiveness of interaction with outside world.</string>
    <string name="infoCpgcon">cPGCON is a post Graduate Conference an annual event, conducted by Board of Studies in Computer Engineering, Savitribai Phule Pune University. This is an effort to develop knowledge sharing by PG Dissertations and Doctoral Research. Post Graduate students and research scholars present their algorithmic and analytical proposals and progress to contribute in the frontiers of domain expertise and innovation. Considering large no. of colleges offering PG courses in Computer engineering academics host of the conferences is rotated to best improvise technical event management skills. Important objective is to develop association with world leading knowledge centers and expertise.</string>
    <string name="infoDepartement">The department of Computer Engineering at PCCoE is committed for value added quality technical education in Computer Engineering. The strong pillars of our department for UG and PG program are the State of the Art Infrastructure, Competent Faculty and hardworking students. In addition to core academics, the students are provided with plenty of opportunities to develop and excel in curricular, co-curricular and extra-curricular areas such as research, skills development, higher studies, industrial training and placements. The program aims towards all round development of the students to make them competent individuals for industry, academia and research.\n\n<b>Vision</b>\nTo be a Premier Hub in Computer Engineering in Education and Research.\n\n<b>Mission</b>\nTo build technologically competent and ethically strong individuals for serving the needs of industry and society by providing state-of-the-art resources, opportunities for Learning and Research in Computer Engineering.\n\n<b>Program Outcomes(POs)</b>\nAn ability to apply the knowledge of computing and mathematics to solve various problems.\n\nAn ability to analyze the problem and define the computing requirements appropriate to its solution.\n\nAn ability to design and develop a computer based system, process, components or program to meet desired needs.\n\nAn ability to use research based knowledge.\n\nAn ability to use current techniques and modern engineering tools necessary for computing practice.\n\nAn ability to analyze the impact of computing solutions with an understanding of social, ethical and environmental issues.\n\nAn ability to work effectively as an individual or as team member to communicate effectively with the range of audiences to achieve a common goal.\n\nAn ability to apply project management principles and practices.\n\nAn ability to recognize the need for and to engage in continual professional development.\n\n<b>Program Educational Objectives (PEOs)</b>\nGraduates of the Programme will leverage Engineering fundamentals in their successful careers.\n\nGraduates of the Programme will exhibit innovation and technological competence in computing all through their careers.\n\nGraduates of the Programme will perform to the expectations of employers, explore the opportunities for higher studies and/or show the awareness of self-business challenges.\n\nGraduates of the Programme will demonstrate ethical practices, lifelong learning with the awareness of needs of the society.</string>
    <string name="infoAcm">Set up in 2012, the PCCoE ACM Student Chapter is striving hard for the development of students. This chapter encourages students to showcase their talents and develop their skills in all aspects.The Chapter which is now in its fourth year is improving rapidly on all counts with the motivating guidance of the faculty sponsors. This Student chapter conducts various activities in accordance with the various cells.
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_second3">SecondActivity3</string>
    <string name="title_activity_second4">SecondActivity4</string>
    <string name="title_activity_how_too_reach">How To Reach</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_track_your_paper_tabbed">TrackYourPaperTabbed</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="link">Assessment Sheet Link:<a href="http://www.google.com" />http://pccoecpgcon2016.com/assessment_sheet.pdf</string>
</resources>
